那么，为什么要采访前端特别如此困难?
So why is interviewing for
front end specifically so difficult?
这个问题有很多答案，但给我一些答案。
There are many answers to this,
but give me some.
把你最好的给我
Give me your best.
> > 科技发展很快。
&gt;&gt; The tech changes quite fast.
>> [LAUGH] 。
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] It does.
如果你想打中你的头就会陷入昏迷
If you were to hit your head
go into a coma wake up,
你根本不知道前头到底发生了什么
you would have no idea what's
going on in front end anymore.
浏览器的工作完全不同，技术完全不同。
Browsers work completely differently,
technology's completely different.
你说什么角
You're like, what's an angular?
有什么意见
What's a view?
那是 MVC的一部分吗
Is that like part of MVC?
他们就像是 [ LAUGH] MVC?
They're like, [LAUGH] MVC?
这个人多大了
How old is this person?
还有别的吗
What else?
为什么采访前线如此困难?
Why is interviewing for
Frontend so difficult?
我有几个
I've got a few.
一，前端是什么 ?
One, what is the Frontend?
可能有那么多东西
It could be so many things.
如果你要编程，我不知道，特斯拉，不是前端，
If you're programming for, I don't know,
a Tesla, is that not a front-end,
和你互动的东西吗
something you interact with?
你在编程，我不知道，冰箱，平板
You're programming, I don't know,
a refrigerator, a tablet for
你的冰箱就在前面
your refrigerator, that's the frontend.
浏览器，台式机，移动设备。
Browsers, desktops, mobile devices.
Fronsay 是如此广泛的范畴，很难说
Frontend is such a broad category
that it's really hard to say
这是前线的一件事只有这件事
this is one thing for
frontend and it's only this.
不不这事太多了
No, no, it's so many broad things.
在所有工程中， UI 可能是最新的。
And of all the parts of engineering,
UI is probably one of the newest.
对， 20， 30 岁，在那里，可能有点大。
Yeah, it's 20, 30 years old,
around there, maybe a little bit older.
但在计算机科学的其他方面
But in terms of other
parts of computer science,
前面的情况还是很新的，而且在迅速发展。
the frontend is still very new and
it's evolving quickly.
还有什么是前端面试，那是疯狂的大。
Also what makes front end interviewing,
it's crazy broad.
太庞大了
It's so huge.
我们可以讨论的话题
The topics we can cover.
如果我说 HTTP 头那是前端
If I said HTTP headers, that's front end.
这绝对是你要处理的事情
That's definitely something you deal with.
其实任何有 HTTP 的东西都希望你知道
Actually anything with HTTP I would
expect you might have to know as
一个前端工程师，这取决于你的工作。
a front end engineer
depending on your job.
无障碍，工人，
Accessibility, workers,
任何排序，浏览器兼容性， CSS，我可以
any sort, browser compatibilities,
CSS, I can
继续做你可能要在Fron趋向工程里做的事情
keep going of the things like you might
have to cover in Frontend engineering.
你可以说，是的，这些是有效的 Fronsend 工程问题。
And you can say, yeah, these are valid
Frontend engineering questions.
嗯。
Yes.
>> 网上他们说这是一个不同类型的
&gt;&gt; The online they're saying
that it's a ton of different
作为一个技能集的报价集在一起。
things that are lumped together
as quote unquote one skill set.
>> 是，我们不知道这些是什么，因为我们不理解
&gt;&gt; Yes, and we don't know what those those
are because again, we don't understand
前面的工程有一半是问题的一半
what frontend engineering is half
the time that's a lot of the problem.
因此，我们一致认为存在一个问题。
So collectively we agree
there's a problem.
还有一个问题，我觉得这很滑稽。
And another problem,
I think this is hilarious.
我没笑我在里面笑
I'm not laughing, I'm laughing inside.
另一个问题是我们都有不同的想法
Another one problem is we all
have a different idea about
核心概念是什么。
what the core concepts are.
在 JavaScript I 中作为作用域的基本内容
Something as foundational
as scope in JavaScript I
那天发了个推文，我收到很多人的回应，
tweeted this out the other day,
I got so many responses from people,
比我的狗画更有反应，我对互联网非常失望。
much more response than my dog pictures,
I'm very disappointed with the Internet.
然后我得到工程师的反应
Then I got response from
engineers weighing in, in much,
比我更聪明的工程师
much smarter engineers than me.
他们对什么范围的定义略有不同
And they all had a slightly different
definition about what scope is
在 JavaScript中。
in JavaScript.
这就是问题的一部分
That's part of the problem is,
我们不分享关于前端工程的集体语言
we don't share this collective language
about what front end engineering is.
Heck，我们甚至不了解 JavaScript 的核心概念
Heck, we don't even understand
the core concepts of JavaScript and
以万万的方式说
just saying that in a universal way.
这也是一个很大的问题。
And that's a lot of the problem too.
我怎么建网站的想法可能跟你的想法不同
My idea of how to build a website is
probably different from your idea of how
来建立一个网站
to build a website.
那么我们如何过去呢 ?
So how do we get past that?
我们如何建立这种水平的领域
How do we establish this
kind of level field
我们知道我们在说什么
where we understand what
we're talking about.
我们可以有效地沟通。
We can communicate effectively.